Let's go for the next one modifying the firewall rules for a lateral moment.
Usually, we are in the process of preparing the RDP for a lateral moment.
So this is the commands to modify the RDP in firewall to allow the RDP protocol in
firewall.
So the RDP protocol will use the port number of 3, 3, 8, 9, double 3, 8, 9.
This is one of the important interview question, 3, 3, 8, 9, that was an RDP port, okay.
So this command will add a rule in a firewall to enable RDP on the machine, okay.
So let's modify this one and now we can see the modification was good and we done with that.
So this will basically modify the firewall, that's all, okay.
So let's hop off from here and we'll continue our discussion in our next video.